<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <name>SmartAssign</name>
    <key>smartassign</key>
    <state>stable</state>
    <logo>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/RPGMais/smartassign/main/pics/smartassign-logo.png</logo>
    <description>
        <short>
            <en_US>This plugin allows the assignment of a ticket using a smartassign policy.</en_US>
            <en_GB>This plugin allows the assignment of a ticket using a smartassign policy.</en_GB>
            <it_IT>Questo plugin permette l'assegnazione di un ticket utilizzando una politica di smartassign.</it_IT>
            <pt_BR>Este plugin permite a atribuição de um chamado utilizando uma política de smartassign.</pt_BR>
            <fr_FR>Ce plugin permet l'attribution d'un ticket en utilisant une politique de smartassign.</fr_FR>
            <es_ES>Este plugin permite la asignación de un ticket utilizando una política de smartassign.</es_ES>
        </short>
        <long>
            <en_US>This plugin allows the automatic assignment and distribution of tickets based on the group responsible for the ITIL category. The plugin operates in two modes: Balancing, where tickets are distributed evenly among the group members, or Rotation, where tickets are assigned alternately.</en_US>
            <en_GB>This plugin allows the automatic assignment and distribution of tickets based on the group responsible for the ITIL category. The plugin operates in two modes: Balancing, where tickets are distributed evenly among the group members, or Rotation, where tickets are assigned alternately.</en_GB>
            <it_IT>Questo plugin permette l'assegnazione e distribuzione automatica dei ticket in base al gruppo responsabile della categoria ITIL. Il plugin opera in due modalità: Bilanciamento, dove i ticket vengono distribuiti equamente tra i membri del gruppo, o Rotazione, dove i ticket vengono assegnati in modo alternato.</it_IT>
            <pt_BR>Atribuição e distribuição automática de chamados com base no grupo responsável pela categoria ITIL. O plugin opera em duas modalidades: Balanceamento, onde os chamados são distribuídos de maneira equilibrada entre os membros do grupo, ou Rodízio, em que os chamados são atribuídos de forma alternada.</pt_BR>
            <fr_FR>Ce plugin permet l'attribution et la distribution automatique des tickets en fonction du groupe responsable de la catégorie ITIL. Le plugin fonctionne en deux modes : Équilibrage, où les tickets sont distribués de manière équilibrée entre les membres du groupe, ou Rotation, où les tickets sont attribués de manière alternée.</fr_FR>
            <es_ES>Este plugin permite la asignación y distribución automática de tickets en función del grupo responsable de la categoría ITIL. El plugin funciona en dos modos: Balanceo, donde los tickets se distribuyen equitativamente entre los miembros del grupo, o Rotación, donde los tickets se asignan de forma alternada.</es_ES>
        </long>
    </description>
    <homepage>https://github.com/RPGMais/smartassign</homepage>
    <download>https://github.com/RPGMais/smartassign/releases</download>
    <issues>https://github.com/RPGMais/smartassign/issues</issues>
    <readme>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/RPGMais/smartassign/master/README.md</readme>
    <authors>
        <author>Richard Loureiro</author>
    </authors>
    <versions>
        <version>
            <num>2.2.0</num>
            <compatibility>~10.0.0</compatibility>
            <download_url>https://github.com/RPGMais/smartassign/releases/download/v2.2.0-beta/smartassign-v2.2.0.tar.gz</download_url>
        </version>
    </versions>
    <langs>
        <lang>en_US</lang>
        <lang>en_GB</lang>
        <lang>pt_BR</lang>
        <lang>es_ES</lang>
        <lang>fr_FR</lang>
        <lang>it_IT</lang>
    </langs>
    <license>GPL v3</license>
    <tags>
        <en_US>
            <tag>Ticket</tag>
            <tag>Helpdesk</tag>
            <tag>Technician</tag>
        </en_US>
        <en_GB>
            <tag>Ticket</tag>
            <tag>Helpdesk</tag>
            <tag>Technician</tag>
        </en_GB>
        <it_IT>
            <tag>Ticket</tag>
            <tag>Assistenza</tag>
            <tag>Tecnico</tag>
        </it_IT>
        <pt_BR>
            <tag>Chamado</tag>
            <tag>Assistência</tag>
            <tag>Técnico</tag>
        </pt_BR>
        <fr_FR>
            <tag>Ticket</tag>
            <tag>Assistance</tag>
            <tag>Technicien</tag>
        </fr_FR>
        <es_ES>
            <tag>Ticket</tag>
            <tag>Soporte</tag>
            <tag>Técnico</tag>
        </es_ES>
    </tags>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/RPGMais/smartassign/refs/heads/main/pics/smartassign.png</screenshot>
    </screenshots>
</root>